Guide to the Asa and Elna Spaulding Papers, 1909-1997 and undated, bulk 1935-1983 RL.01240
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Asa Spaulding Subgroup, 1909-1984 and undated, 331 boxes
  - Audiovisual Materials Series, 1950-1980s and undated, 4 boxes
    - Video Materials Subseries,1957-1958 and undated
      - Subject Files Sub-subseries,1957-1958 and undated
        - OR23. Untitled, undated (8mm film, color) (Box AV-4)
        - OR24. Untitled, undated, possibly film of Asa Spaulding giving a speech (16mm film, b/w.) (Box AV-4)
        - OR25. Untitled, labeled as "Dub for Dr. A.T. Spaulding, Sr.," undated (U-matic videocassette, 13:00") (Box AV-4)
  - Oversize Materials, 1909, 1952-1981 and undated, 3 boxes
    - Writings and Speeches Series,1960-1968
      - Asa Spaulding Autobiography Research Material (clippings on Spaulding), 1960-1967 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
      - Asa Spaulding Autobiography Research Material (clippings on North Carolina Mutual), 1962-1964 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
      - Works by Other Authors: C. Vann Woodward, 1968 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
    - Organizations Series,1952-1980
      - Democratic National Convention memorabilia,1980 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Services Co. Minority Analysis Program, circa 1971 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
      - White Rock Baptist Church calendars,1952, 1954-1965, 1967-1968 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
    - North Carolina Mutual Files Series,1909, 1944, 1963
      - Financial and Operating Charts,1963 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
      - Pension Plans,1944 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
      - Valuation of Business in Force in North and South Carolina,1909 Dec. 31 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
    - Insurance Files Series,1965
      - National Insurance Association,1965 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
    - Subject Files Series,1964-1966, 1981
      - Awards,1964-1966 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
      - Biographical: photograph of silver anniversary of the Class of 1930, New York University School of Commerce, Hotel Delmonico, New York, N.Y., 1955 May 24 (Oversize-box AOM-3)
      - Memorabilia (calendar),1981 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
      - Newspapers and clippings
        - The Afro-American (Baltimore),1961, 1976, 1983, 3 items (Oversize-box AOM-1)
        - The Carolina Times (Durham, N.C.),1959, 1979-1980, 3 items (Oversize-box AOM-1)
        - The Charlotte Post, 1959 (Oversize-box AOM-1)
        - The Hilltop (Howard University),1968-1983, 17 items in 4 folders (Oversize-box AOM-2)
        - The Howard Underwriter (Howard University),1978-1982, 4 items (Oversize-box AOM-2)
        - The Tuskeegeean (Ala.),1980 (Oversize-box AOM-2)
        - The Washington Afro-American, 1975-1979, 4 items (Oversize-box AOM-2)
        - The Wilmington Journal (N.C.), 1979 (Oversize-box AOM-2)
        - Various clippings,1959-1981 (Oversize-box AOM-2)
        - Various small newspapers, single issues,1976-1983, 8 items (Oversize-box AOM-2)
- Elna Spaulding Subgroup, 1909-1997 and undated, bulk 1970s-1983, 34 boxes
  The Elna Spaulding Subgroup is arranged in three general subject series: Correspondence, Organizations, and Subject Files. In addition, two series whose arrangement was dictated by the physical format of the materials add supporting material:Photographic Materials and Oversize Materials. Details about the arrangement of each of these series are contained in their respective series notes.
  - Correspondence Series, 1928-1989, bulk 1970-1983, 4 boxes
    Correspondence from individuals and organizations. Prominent or frequent correspondents have individually labeled folders; others appear in folders labeled for each letter of the alphabet. Individuals and organizations are arranged in one alphabetical sequence. Researchers should also consult the Organizations Series for any organizations that appear here.
    - A, 1974-1982 (Box EC-1, Folder 1)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, AZO Chapter, 1977-1982 (Box EC-1, Folder 2)
    - Andrews, Ike, 1974-1980 (Box EC-1, Folder 3)
    - B, 1974-1983 (Box EC-1, Folder 4)
    - Bridgeforth, 1976-1980 (Box EC-1, Folder 5)
    - C, 1928-1982 (Box EC-1, Folder 6)
    - Child Advocacy Commission of Durham, Inc., 1976-1980 (Box EC-1, Folder 7)
    - D, 1930-1983 (Box EC-1, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Executive Committee (Durham and North Carolina), 1980-1982 (Box EC-1, Folder 9)
    - Duke University (assorted councils and departments), 1976-1983 (Box EC-1, Folder 10)
    - Duke University Medical Center: Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development, 1981-1983 (Box EC-1, Folder 11)
    - Durham CETA (Employment and Training Office), 1978-1982 (Box EC-1, Folder 12)
    - Durham Chamber of Commerce, 1976-1983 (Box EC-1, Folder 13)
    - Durham College, 1976-1978 (Box EC-2, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, 1976-1983 (Box EC-2, Folder 2)
    - Durham County Schools, 1976-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 3)
    - Durham Day Care Council, 1979-1983 (Box EC-2, Folder 4)
    - E, 1974-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 5)
    - F, 1974-1983 (Box EC-2, Folder 6)
    - G, 1967-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 7)
    - H, 1973-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 8)
    - Helms, Jesse, 1977-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 9)
    - I, 1972-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 10)
    - J, 1974-1981 (Box EC-2, Folder 11)
    - Joint Action in Community Service, 1976-1977, undated (Box EC-2, Folder 12)
    - K, 1974-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 13)
    - L, 1974-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 14)
    - League of Women Voters, 1973-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 15)
    - M, 1967-1982 (Box EC-2, Folder 16)
    - N, 1976-1982 (Box EC-3, Folder 1)
    - National Council of Negro Women, 1980-1982 (Box EC-3, Folder 2)
    - O, 1974-1982 (Box EC-3, Folder 3)
    - P, 1976-1982 (Box EC-3, Folder 4)
    - Q, 1979 Aug. 29 (Box EC-3, Folder 5)
    - R, 1933-1982 (Box EC-3, Folder 6)
    - Russell, Datie Mae Bridgeforth, 1973-1982 (Box EC-3, Folder 7)
    - Russell, Hattie, 1972-1981 (Box EC-3, Folder 8)
    - S, 1973-1982 (Box EC-3, Folder 9)
    - Scott, Marie B., 1976-1982 (Box EC-3, Folder 10)
    - Spaulding Family, 1968-1982 (Box EC-3, Folder 11)
    - Spaulding, Aaron L., 1964 June 11-1965 Nov. 6 (Box EC-3, Folder 12)
    - Spaulding Asa T., Sr., 1930 Sept. 25-1931 Jan. 23 (Box EC-4, Folder 1)
    - Spaulding Asa T., Sr., 1931 Jan. 24-April 30 (Box EC-4, Folder 2)
    - Spaulding Asa T., Sr., 1931 May 2-1932 Feb. 6, 1937-1939, 1944, 1960, 1978-1981, and n.d. (Box EC-4, Folder 3)
    - T, 1976-1981 (Box EC-4, Folder 4)
    - U, 1976-1982 and undated (Box EC-4, Folder 5)
    - United Church of Religious Service, 1976-1980 (Box EC-4, Folder 6)
    - V, 1980-1982 (Box EC-4, Folder 7)
    - W, 1931-1982 (Box EC-4, Folder 8)
    - Y-Z, 1974-1977 (Box EC-4, Folder 9)
    - Unknown Senders, A-Z, 1929-1931, 1974-1982, and undated (Box EC-4, Folder 10)
  - Organizations Series, 1968-1983, 24 boxes, 2 oversize folders
    Meeting agendas, minutes, financial and annual reports, printed material, and some correspondence from a variety of political bodies and activist organizations. By far the largest group of material is that relating to the Durham County Board of Commissioners. Other major groups represented include the Lincoln Community Health Center, the National Council for Negro Women, the White House Conference on Aging, and Women-in-Action for the Prevention of Violence and its Causes. Arranged alphabetically by name of organization.
    - A, 1973-1982 (Box EO-1, Folder 1)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, 1976 Sept.-1982 Oct. (Box EO-1, Folder 2)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, 1982 Dec.-1983, n.d. (Box EO-1, Folder 3)
    - American Dance Festival, 1980-1981 (Box EO-1, Folder 4)
    - B, 1876-1982 (Box EO-1, Folder 5)
    - C, 1973-1982 (Box EO-1, Folder 6)
    - Capital Health Systems Agency, 1977-1981 (Box EO-1, Folder 7)
    - Capital Health Systems Agency, May-June 1982 (Box EO-1, Folder 8)
    - Capital Health Systems Agency, June-Aug. 3, 1982 (Box EO-1, Folder 9)
    - Capital Health Systems Agency, 1982 Aug. 18-1983 Jan. 19 (Box EO-2, Folder 1)
    - Capital Health Systems Agency, 1983 Jan. 20-Feb. 17 (Box EO-2, Folder 2)
    - Capital Health Systems Agency, 1983 Feb. 28-April, n.d. (Box EO-2, Folder 3)
    - Child Advocacy Commission, 1977-1981, undated (Box EO-2, Folder 4)
    - Clean Community Systems, 1981-1982, undated (Box EO-2, Folder 5)
    - Congressional Black Caucus, 1976-1981, undated (Box EO-2, Folder 6)
    - Coordinating Council for Senior Citizens, 1981-1982 (Box EO-2, Folder 7)
    - Council for Women of Durham County, 1982-1983 (Box EO-2, Folder 8)
    - D, 1976-1982 (Box EO-2, Folder 9)
    - Democratic Women, 1978-1983 (Box EO-2, Folder 10)
    - Democrats, Black, 1976 (Box EO-3, Folder 1)
    - Democrats, Durham and North Carolina, 1976-1983, undated (Box EO-3, Folder 2)
    - Democrats, Young, 1979-1982 (Box EO-3, Folder 3)
    - Duke University Medical Center: Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development, 1976-1981 Fall (Box EO-3, Folder 4)
    - Duke University Medical Center: Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development, 1981 Fall-1983 (Box EO-3, Folder 5)
    - Duke University Medical Center: Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development, n.d. (Box EO-3, Folder 6)
    - Duke University Continuing Education, 1976-1981, undated (Box EO-3, Folder 7)
    - Durham Advisory Board to Duke Hospital, 1974-1976 Sept. (Box EO-3, Folder 8)
    - Durham Advisory Board to Duke Hospital, 1976 Oct.-1982 (Box EO-3, Folder 9)
    - Durham Arts Council, 1977-1982, undated (Box EO-3, Folder 10)
    - Durham CETA (Employment and Training Office), 1978-1980 June (Box EO-3, Folder 11)
    - Durham CETA (Employment and Training Office), 1980 Dec.-1982 (Box EO-4, Folder 1)
    - [Greater] Durham Chamber of Commerce, 1976-1982 (Box EO-4, Folder 2)
    - Durham College, 1977-1978 (Box EO-4, Folder 3)
    - Durham Committee on the Affairs of Black People, 1979-1981 (Box EO-4, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, 1971 (Box EO-4, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, 1974 (Box EO-4, Folder 6)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Mar. 26-Oct. 20, 1975 (Box EO-4, Folder 7)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Nov.-Dec. 1975 (Box EO-4, Folder 8)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, 1976 (Box EO-4, Folder 9)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Jan.-May 1977 (Box EO-4, Folder 10)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, May-July 1977 (Box EO-5, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, July-August 1977 (Box EO-5, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, August-Nov. 1977 (Box EO-5, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, April 24-May 3, 1978 (Box EO-5, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, May 3-May 15, 1978 (Box EO-5, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, May 16-17, 1978 (Box EO-5, Folder 6)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, May 23, 1978 (Box EO-6, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, May 29-Sept. 1978 (Box EO-6, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, 1978 Real or Personal Property Complaints (Box EO-6, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Feb.-June 1979 (Box EO-6, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Sept.-Dec. 1979 (Box EO-6, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, 1979 (Box EO-6, Folder 6)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal Year starting July 1, 1979 (Box EO-7, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Jan. 7-May 19, 1980 (Box EO-7, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, May 19-June 20, 1980 (Box EO-7, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, June 22-July 25, 1980 (Box EO-7, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, July 30-Sept. 22, 1980 (Box EO-7, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Sept. 30-Oct. 1980 (Box EO-8, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Nov. 1980 (Box EO-8, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Dec. 1980 and undated (Box EO-8, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal Year starting July 1, 1980 (1 of 2) (Box EO-8, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal Year starting July 1, 1980 (2 of 2) (Box EO-8, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Jan.-Feb. 24, 1981 (Box EO-8, Folder 6)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Jan-Mar. 1981 (Box EO-9, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Feb. 25-March 16, 1981 (Box EO-9, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, March-April 1981 (Box EO-9, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, May-June 1981 (Box EO-9, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, July-August 1981 (Box EO-9, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Sept.-Nov. 1981 (Box EO-9, Folder 6)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Dec. 1981 (Box EO-10, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, 1981 (Box EO-10, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal year starting July 1, 1981 (1 of 4) (Box EO-10, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal year starting July 1, 1981 (2 of 4) (Box EO-10, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal year starting July 1, 1981 (3 of 4) (Box EO-10, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal year starting July 1, 1981 (4 of 4) (Box EO-10, Folder 6)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Jan.-Feb. 11, 1982 (Box EO-11, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Feb. 12-April 5, 1982 (Box EO-11, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, April 22-June 7, 1982 (Box EO-11, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, June 9-20, 1982 (Box EO-11, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, July 6-Aug. 5, 1982 (Box EO-11, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Aug. 13-Sept. 1982 (Box EO-11, Folder 6)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Oct.-Nov. 1, 1982 (Box EO-12, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Nov. 4-Dec. 1982 (Box EO-12, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, 1982 (Box EO-12, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal year starting July 1, 1982 (1 of 3) (Box EO-12, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal year starting July 1, 1982 (2 of 3) (Box EO-12, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Fiscal year starting July 1, 1982 (3 of 3) (Box EO-12, Folder 6)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Jan. 1-4, 1983 (Box EO-13, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Jan. 4-Feb. 2, 1983 (Box EO-13, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Feb. 3-Mar. 6, 1983 (Box EO-13, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, Mar. 16-June 1983 (Box EO-13, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, 1983 (Box EO-13, Folder 5)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, undated (1 of 2) (Box EO-13, Folder 6)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Board of Commissioners, undated (2 of 2) (Box EO-13, Folder 7)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Health Dept., 1974-1977 (Box EO-14, Folder 1)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Health Dept., 1979-1980 (Box EO-14, Folder 2)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Health Dept., Mar.-Dec. 1982 (Box EO-14, Folder 3)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Health Dept., Jan.-Mar. 1983 (Box EO-14, Folder 4)
    - Durham County (N.C.) Library, 1980-1983 (Box EO-14, Folder 5)
    - Durham County Mental Health, 1981-1982 Jan. (Box EO-14, Folder 6)
    - Durham Public Schools (Durham County, N.C.), 1976-1979 (Box EO-14, Folder 7)
    - Durham Day Care Council, 1976-1980 (Box EO-15, Folder 1)
    - Durham Day Care Council, 1981-July 1982 (Box EO-15, Folder 2)
    - Durham Day Care Council, Aug.-Nov. 1982 and undated (Box EO-15, Folder 3)
    - Durham Life Broadcasting, Inc., 1979-1981 (Box EO-15, Folder 4)
    - E, 1978-1982 (Box EO-15, Folder 5)
    - F, 1977-1982 (Box EO-15, Folder 6)
    - Foundation for Better Health of Durham, 1980-1982 (Box EO-15, Folder 7)
    - G, 1982 (Box EO-15, Folder 8)
    - H, 1976-1981 (Box EO-15, Folder 9)
    - I, 1979, undated (Box EO-15, Folder 10)
    - Institute of Government, 1974-1981 (Box EO-15, Folder 11)
    - International Year of the Child Committee, 1979, undated (Box EO-15, Folder 12)
    - J, 1980 (Box EO-15, Folder 13)
    - Joint Action in Community Service, 1974-1980 (Box EO-15, Folder 14)
    - K, 1974-1981 (Box EO-15, Folder 15)
    - L, 1976-1982, undated (Box EO-15, Folder 16)
    - League of Women Voters, 1976-1983 (Box EO-15, Folder 17)
    - Limestone County Extension Service, 1977-1978 (Box EO-16, Folder 1)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, 1975-June 1976 (Box EO-16, Folder 2)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, July 1976-June 1977 (Box EO-16, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, Aug. 1976-Apr. 1977 (Box EO-16, Folder 4)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, May 1977-Feb. 1979 (Box EO-16, Folder 5)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, Mar. 1979-June 1980 (Box EO-16, Folder 6)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, July-Aug. 1980 (Box EO-17, Folder 1)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, Sept.-Dec. 1980 (Box EO-17, Folder 2)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, Dec. 1980-May 1981 (Box EO-17, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, June 1981 (Box EO-17, Folder 4)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, July 1981-Aug. 1982 (Box EO-17, Folder 5)
    - Lincoln Community Health Center, Sept. 1982-1983 and undated (Box EO-17, Folder 6)
    - The Links, Inc., 1973-1982 (Box EO-18, Folder 1)
    - The Links, Inc., 1983 and undated (Box EO-18, Folder 2)
    - M, 1976-1981 (Box EO-18, Folder 3)
    - N, 1974-1982 (Box EO-18, Folder 4)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1980-1981 (Box EO-18, Folder 5)
    - National Association of Black County Officials, National Association of Counties, 1977-1980 (Box EO-18, Folder 6)
    - National Association of Broadcasters, 1977 (Box EO-18, Folder 7)
    - National Black Child Development Institute, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box EO-18, Folder 8)
    - National Caucus and Center on Black Aged, Inc., 1981, undated (Box EO-18, Folder 9)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1970-1982 (Box EO-18, Folder 10)
    - National Council for Negro Women, 1976-Feb. 22, 1981 (Box EO-18, Folder 11)
    - National Council for Negro Women, Feb. 23-Sept. 1981 (Box EO-19, Folder 1)
    - National Council for Negro Women, Oct.-Dec. 1981 (Box EO-19, Folder 2)
    - National Council for Negro Women, 1982 (Box EO-19, Folder 3)
    - National Council for Negro Women, undated (Box EO-19, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina Association of County Commissioners, 1976-June 1982 (Box EO-19, Folder 5)
    - North Carolina Association of County Commissioners, June 1982-1983 and undated (Box EO-19, Folder 6)
    - North Carolina Association of Minority Public Officials, 1977-1982 (Box EO-19, Folder 7)
    - North Carolina Central University, 1979-1982 (Box EO-19, Folder 8)
    - North Carolina Central University: Museum of Art, 1973-1981 (Box EO-19, Folder 9)
    - North Carolina Central University: Museum of Art, 1982-1983 and undated (Box EO-20, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina Council of Women's Organization, 1971-1982 (Box EO-20, Folder 2)
    - North Carolina Department of Cultural Resources, 1976-1982 (Box EO-20, Folder 3)
    - North Carolina Museum of Life and Science, 1976-1981, undated (Box EO-20, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina School of the Arts, 1973-1975 (Box EO-20, Folder 5)
    - North Carolina School of the Arts, 1976-1981 (Box EO-20, Folder 6)
    - O, 1972-1982 (Box EO-20, Folder 7)
    - Operation Breakthrough, Inc., 1973-1982 (Box EO-20, Folder 8)
    - P, 1979-1980 (Box EO-20, Folder 9)
    - Political Action Committee for Education (PACE), 1976-1980 (Box EO-20, Folder 10)
    - R, 1973-1982 (Box EO-20, Folder 11)
    - S, 1976-1982 (Box EO-20, Folder 12)
    - Stagville Preservation Center, Inc., 1976-1981 (Box EO-20, Folder 13)
    - Stagville Preservation Center, Inc., 1982-1983 and undated (Box EO-20, Folder 14)
    - State of North Carolina, 1979-1982 (Box EO-20, Folder 15)
    - T, 1976-1982 (Box EO-21, Folder 1)
    - Talladega College Alumni Association, 1977-1982 (Box EO-21, Folder 2)
    - Today's Women Organization, 1980-1981 (Box EO-21, Folder 3)
    - Triangle J Council of Governments, 1976-1981 (Box EO-21, Folder 4)
    - Triangle J Council of Governments, 1982-1983 (Box EO-21, Folder 5)
    - Triangle J Council of Governments: Project 2000, 1981 (Box EO-21, Folder 6)
    - Triangle J Council of Governments: Project 2000, 1982 and undated (Box EO-21, Folder 7)
    - United Church of Religious Service, 1980-1982, undated (Box EO-21, Folder 8)
    - United Fund of Durham and Durham Co., Inc., Jan.-Feb. 1982 (Box EO-21, Folder 9)
    - United Health Service (UHS) for Alcohol and Drug Abuse, 1978-1982 (Box EO-21, Folder 10)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, 1974-1982 (Box EO-21, Folder 11)
    - Urban Ministries, 1982-1983 (Box EO-21, Folder 12)
    - Voter Education Project (VEP), 1976 (Box EO-21, Folder 13)
    - W, 1977-1982 (Box EO-22, Folder 1)
    - The White House, 1979-1980 (Box EO-22, Folder 2)
    - White House Conference on Aging, Feb-Nov. 1, 1981 (Box EO-22, Folder 3)
    - White House Conference on Aging, Nov. 5-Dec. 14, 1981 (Box EO-22, Folder 4)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1982 and undated (Box EO-22, Folder 5)
    - White House Conference on Aging. Committees and Information, 1981 (Box EO-22, Folder 6)
    - White House Conference on Aging. Committees and Information, 1981 (Box EO-22, Folder 7)
    - White House Conference on Aging. Recommendations, 1981 (Box EO-23, Folder 1)
    - White House Conference on Aging. Recommendations, 1981 (Box EO-23, Folder 2)
    - Women-in-Action for the Prevention of Violence and Its Causes, 1968-1974 (Box EO-23, Folder 3)
    - Women-in-Action for the Prevention of Violence and Its Causes, 1975-1979 (Box EO-23, Folder 4)
    - Women-in-Action for the Prevention of Violence and Its Causes, 1977-1982 and undated (Box EO-23, Folder 5)
    - Women-in-Action for the Prevention of Violence and Its Causes, Scrapbook, 1970s (Box EO-24, Folder 1)
    - Women's Forum of North Carolina, 1977-1978 (Box EO-24, Folder 2)
    - WTVD, 1973-1979 (Box EO-24, Folder 3)
    - WTVD, 1980-1981 (Box EO-24, Folder 4)
    - YWCA, 1976-1982 (Box EO-24, Folder 5)
    - Durham Urban Area Thoroughfare Plan, 1980 March 24 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Appendix B: Traffic Court Location, 1971 October (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Durham County Maps from Dept. of Transportation (3), 1980 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Utility/Flood Plain and Development/Zoning Maps, 1981 May 25 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Durham County Dept. of Transportation Maps (3), 1980 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Durham County Dept. of Transportation Maps (3), 1982 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Subject Files Series, 1909-1997 and undated, bulk 1974-1982, 3 boxes
    Series consists mainly of documents related to Elna Spaulding's political campaigns for the office of Durham County Commissioner. Also included here are some biographical data and miscellaneous writings. Arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Awards and Programs, 1983-1997 (Box ES-1, Folder 1)
    - Biographical data, 1909-1982 and undated (Box ES-1, Folder 2)
    - Calendars, Appointments, and Contacts, 1976-1982 (Box ES-1, Folder 3)
    - Calendars, Appointments, and Contacts, 1976-1982 (Box ES-1, Folder 4)